Lazime Toshi

Tirana, Albania | +355684284658 | toshi.lazime@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/lazime-toshi | https://github.com/latolatto

SKILLS

Technical Skills: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, Express.js, EJS, SQL, MySQL, PostgreSQL, PHP, RESTful APIs, Git, Github

Soft Skills: Quick Witted, Hardworking, Great Communication, Teamwork, Problem Solving, Output-Driven

Languages: Albanian (native), English (full professional proficiency)

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Front-End e-Commerce Website Development (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript) Developed a responsive e-commerce website for an online ticketing store and infopoint, featuring product listings, shopping cart functionality, order processing using local storage and payment integration using PayPal. https://touristsolutions.info/

Front-End e-Commerce Website Development (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript) Developed a responsive e-commerce website for an online store, featuring product listings, shopping cart functionality, and order processing using local storage. https://shopathletics.store/

Joke Generator Web App using a public API and Node.js

A web-based joke generator that fetches jokes from the JokeAPI. Users can select joke categories and customize their experience. Built with Node.js, Express.js, and EJS, the application dynamically renders jokes and offers a simple, interactive interface. https://github.com/latolatto/joke-generator

- **Front-End Website Development** (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript) Designed and developed a dynamic and responsive website for a social media marketing agency. The site features interactive elements, detailed service pages, and a user-friendly contact form. https://hexamarketing.co/
- **Front-End e-Commerce Website Development** (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, ¡Query) Developed a comprehensive responsive e-commerce platform for an wood working business, featuring product listings, shopping cart functionality, and order processing using local storage. https://drutech.co/
- **User Authentication (Login And Sign-Up) Systems** Developed secure login and sign-up systems with user authentication and data validation. Utilized HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, and MySQL to ensure seamless functionality and a user-friendly interface.
- Form Handling And Validation Systems (Search & Submission) Developed secure and user-friendly form handling systems for search and submission functionalities. Utilized HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, and MySQL to create dynamic forms with real-time validation and efficient backend integration.

Lazime Toshi

EDUCATION

Bootcamp - Full Stack Web Development

App Brewery

(2023-2024)Online

Master Of Science in Business Information Systems

University of Tirana

Bachelor's Degree in Finance

(2021-2023)Tirana, Albania

University of Tirana

GPA: 8.76/10

GPA: 8.48/10

(2018-2021)Tirana, Albania

WORK HISTORY

Web Developer

Freelance

(Feb 2024 - Present)

Tasks:

- Designing and building custom (primarily front-end) websites, including eCommerce platforms, tailored to client needs with responsive layouts and user-friendly functionality.
- Collaborating with clients to refine project requirements and implementing ongoing updates and improvements.

Part-Time Management & Sales Assistant

(2016 - 2024)

Convenience store, Tirana

Tasks:

- Provided administrative support, including managing documentation, maintaining records of cash flow, overseeing debits and credits.
- Demonstrated adeptness in warehouse operations by actively contributing to inventory management processes.

Telemarketing Operator

(Jul 2018 - Oct 2018)

Tregi Marketing Group, Tirana

Tasks:

- Conducted outbound calls to prospective clients to promote and sell food campaign products.
- Addressed customer inquiries, upselling products effectively.
- Resolved issues promptly, maintaining high customer satisfaction .

HONORS & AWARDS

- Certificate of Excellence (Huawei, 2022) For outstanding results & active work during Huawei Seeds For The Future Program, ranking within top 5 highest results student in Europe.
- TOP European TECH4GOOD Team (Team Leader) (Huawei, 2022) Outstanding work in the TECH4GOOD Global Competition & eagerness for teamwork in developing ideas to contribute for changing the world for the better.